mybanglamp3.com 2016-06-08

# Untitled Document

PRIVACY POLICY  
Effective DEC, 2006  

Welcome to MybanglaMp3.com. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it.

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavor to  
post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This consumer privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source.

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
We have several areas where members can submit information to us, and we also have features that automatically collect information from our members and other users.

INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US.  
We have certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us:  

* Communications with Us. We have features where you can submit information  
to us (such as when contacting us with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

* Communications with Friends. Our site may also have certain features that allow you to send information to others (such as "Mail a song"). We will use the contact information you enter for your friends only to send the email, and then we will delete it from our system.

AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION

Cookies. We use a software technology called "cookies" for several purposes, depending on the type of cookie employed. Within mybanglamp3.com, we use what are commonly called "session" cookies, meaning that they only last as long as you are online. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called "persistent" cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be prepopulated for you. This cookie is only offered in conjunction with certain Affiliate Sites that choose to make it available and it can only be activated if you select that option during your sign-in. If you select this option you can always deselect it each time you sign-in.

Other. In order to personalize our service for your enjoyment and to monitor and improve the performance of our technology, we do collect/capture other data such as a member's searches (such as their search criteria and results) and the music they listened to. We only share search history or music usage data on an aggregate basis.

For our internal purposes, we gather information such as date, time, connection speed and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information simply for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration.

Third Party Advertising  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick(Google Ads),FoxNetworks etc who are our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about the ads served visit the respective ad partner website.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

We do not share your personally identifiable information with other  
companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission.

We may share (provide and receive) with others certain aggregate service information, which is not personally identifiable. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

SECURITY

MybanglaMp3.com endeavors to protect the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We use secure SSL technology to protect the transmission of sensitive information such as your registration, login, and credit card information.

We store your personal information on a secure server, and use special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

ACCESS/CHOICE

You will always have access to your registration information, which you can modify at any time by clicking on the "Edit Profile" subsection of the "My Account" area of the site, so long as you continue to provide us with certain information required to maintain your subscription (such as a valid email address). Also, marketing e-mails from mybanglamp3.com will come with instructions for unsubscribing from our email mailing list.

LINKS

We may display links to other sites within MybanglaMp3.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

CONTACT US:

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of mybanglamp3.com, you can contact:

webmaster@mybanglamp3.com
